lottomadness.net 2016-10-27

# JACKPOT DIRECTORY

This website is a part of Perfect Internet Inc. DBA “UNICORN” ([www.unicorn.network](http://www.perfectinter.net/)) and adheres to the following privacy policy.

This privacy policy describes how we collect and use your data. If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy or its enforcement, please feel free to contact us. 

On today’s Internet where oftentimes anything goes, many companies out there use the guise of offering free stuff to collect and sell your data, send you spam, and even infect your computer with viruses, malware, and spyware. We hate spam, scams, and all that crap just as much as you do.

Your data is safe with us; we will never rent, sell, or share your data with anyone outside of our network (unless required by law), nor will we build a personal profile about you to track you for advertising purposes. That is our commitment to our members, a safe place to have the perfect Internet experience while receiving amazing rewards and benefits— UNICORN.

If you are joining UNICORN **** through an invite of another member, they will receive your name, email, and basic data in order to help you and keep you updated as needed. 

All of our network and partner websites have committed to these same privacy standards, so you know that they are sites you can trust.

**UNICORN Privacy Policy Details**  
UNICORN **** is a network of websites with members from all over the world. We collect information that our users submit to us such as their name and email address to allow us to identify users and notify them of changes or updates to our service. We also collect personal information submitted by our users in filling out their profile on the service such as gender, location, age, etc. We collect this personal information when our users do activities on the service such as but not limited to sign up as a member; make changes to their member profile information; and send email messages. 

Like many other websites, UNICORN uses a standard technology called "cookies." Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive - not on our site. They can help make the Internet experience quicker and more convenient. Cookies allow our users to login without entering their ID and password each time they use UNICORN. Members who disable cookies will not be able to use Perfect Internet. 

All data we collect or track is used only to improve your user experience, reward you, and verify your account.

Please be aware that whenever members voluntarily disclose personal information publicly online - e.g., message boards, file uploads, and public chat communications - that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others. By posting personal information online like in public forums, members may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.

UNICORN **** has a ZERO TOLERANCE for SPAM; if you ever feel another member is spamming you, contact us immediately.

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Notice of changes to this Privacy Policy will be prominently displayed across UNICORN websites after MEMBER login and your continued use of any and all UNICORN websites represents your agreement to the updated Privacy Policy. All rights reserved.

Privacy Policy last updated May 2, 2016
